

Cody Brunner

Software Developer

🚄 Based in Colombia 뾜 US Citizen 🐶 Dog Dad

me@codybrunner.com

https://github.com/rockchalkwushock https://www.linkedin.com/in/cody-brunner/

Summary

AWS Certified Front End developer with more than 4 years experience working with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, and TypeScript. Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks, with extensive knowledge of UX and user psychology. I have had the chance to work with very ambitious startups and small/mid-sized businesses around the world. In my spare time I enjoy tinkering with networks, running, learning and I am slowly, becoming a Whiskey fiend.

Languages

JavaScript/TypeScript

Python Elixir Rust

Cloud, Storage & Databases

AWS Docker MongoDB PostgreSOL Technologies & Frameworks

Absinthe - Cypress - Django - ExpressJS - Fly.io - GatsbyJS - MSW - NextJS - Phoenix/LiveView ReactJS - Git - GraphQL

(Apollo) - Jest React-Query - ReduxJS -Storybook - Supabase - Vite

Styling

Bootstrap - ChakraUI - CSS-in-JS CSS3 - Sass - TailwindCSS

Selected Work History

Feb 2022 - Present

Front End Developer @ Appointlet, W US Remote

Appointlet is a cloud-based appointment scheduling solution that helps businesses to connect with users.

My core duties include:

- · Accelerating and optimizing the transformation of the web-app with the CEO and PM to deliver requested features to improve the overall user experience.
- Generated +50K in revenue by enhancing the response times of the product's front end.
- Collaborating with the back end development team to implement new features across the product.
- Liasing with the CS team to address user feedback and concerns acting as user advocate, Monitoring app performance and rectifying front-end-related issues.

Apr-Jun 2022

Fullstack Developer @ Weeldi , | France Remote

Weeldi provides website to API conversion tool using no-code / low code solutions.

- Assessed and collaborated with the Principal Engineer and CTO on overhaul to UI/UX of the product using Material Design and Bootstrap UI Kit.
- Overhauled the consolidation of client-side code out of Phoenix and into ReactJS.

Sept 2021- Feb 2022

Senior Developer @ Lean Tech & Arrive Logistics 🚄 Colombia

B2B tech services company

- Participated delivering UI/UX updates and new features to the XLR8 platform along Arrive Logistics Tech Lead.
- Led and managed a team of 5 developers on various internal projects.
- Participated in peer code reviews as appropriate for the task at hand and reviewed others' code when required.
- Spearheaded several hands-on workshops in technologies such as **GraphQL**.
- Mentored junior developers to help them learn how to code and take their career to the next level.

Sept 2018 -Apr 2021 Web Developer @ <u>Appointlet</u>, Web US

- Upgraded the application from Django REST to Django GraphQL and Angular 1 to ApolloGraphQL, Bootstrap 4, ReactJS, Sass, and TypeScript.
- Acted as principal developer for the V5 version of the client-side application.
- Pioneered and maintained the Chrome/ Edge/Firefox extension
- Launched and maintained the JavaScript SDK.

Education

2015 Wichita Area Technical College - KS

A.A.S Robotic Technology

2011 Kansas Wesleyan University, 2011

B.A. Criminal Justice & Sociology

Home | codybrunner.com

Blog Here are the latest posts from my blog. I write about many things, but mostly you find articles on technology and my experiences as an expat. Contact Me You can schedule a time to chat with me via phone or Google Meet using Appointlet; and if you are interested in hiring me grab my resume below.



https://codybrunner.com/

GitHub - rockchalkwushock/rehype-code-titles: Rehype plugin for parsing code blocks and adding titles to code blocks

Rehype plugin for parsing code blocks and adding titles to code blocks I moved my blog over to using mdx-bundler which uses under the hood to parse the markdown and MDX files. I was using remark-code-titles prior to this move and unfortunately it no longer worked.

nttps://github.com/rockchalkwushock/rehype-code-titles

rehype-code-titles

Rehype plugin for parsing code blocks and adding titles to code blocks



GitHub - rockchalkwushock/chakra: Chakra is a URL Shortener written using Phoenix Framework

You can't perform that action at this time. You signed in with another tab or window. You signed out in another tab or window. Reload to refresh your session. Reload to refresh your session.

https://github.com/rockchalkwushock/chakra

chakra

Framework



Can't wait to see what we build together, See me in action!

Cody Brunner 1